Good evening everyone. This is Satsuki Sugawara from Nogizaka46.
This week, the weekly NogizakaNews has started again!
Yay!
Today is the 8th edition of the Weekly Nogizaka News.
Due to a scheduling conflict, we are recording today's edition for your listening pleasure.
I can't do it while reading your comments, but...
I'll try my best to make you feel as if I'm delivering the news in real time.
I'll try my best to make it sound like I'm delivering it to you in real time.
This is the second time for me to record.
It's the second time I've recorded, but I'm more nervous when I'm recording.
It's a little sad when there are no comments.
I'm also looking at the archived comments a lot.
I'd love it if you could comment in real time, even though it's a recording.
I'd be very happy if you could comment on the recording and I'll be watching too.
And I wonder if anyone has noticed...
This time, too, we're presenting it in a horizontal format.
I've renewed it a little bit, and I'd like to present it in this style.
It's very innovative, isn't it?
I'm so glad that you can see my face even when I'm like this.
Now then, I'm sure you all remember me by now.
But there may be some of you who are watching for the first time today.
I'd like to give you a brief explanation of the program.
I, Satsuki Sugawara, am the MC for this program.
We broadcast live every Monday night.
Today's show is taped, but we usually deliver it live.
We're here to help you with your work
And the latest news from Nogizaka46
We'll keep you updated on the latest news from Nogizaka46.
Until the next episode
The archive will be open to the public.
If you missed it
If you missed it, please check the archive.
We'll be glad to hear from you.
Let us know what you think!
Please use the hashtag “Weekly Nogizaka News” and post your thoughts on social networking sites.
Please post your comments on social networking sites.
Thank you very much!
8 times already!
I wonder if any of you have seen it.
If you're a fan of mine...
I believe you are watching!
I believe you're watching.
I've already memorized the words of the cat.
I'd be happy if you could see so many of them.
I'd be very happy.
I hope you've seen it so many times that you've memorized the word “swing”.
Lately...
The 13th Blanco
The 13th Blanco project.
We're Gisaka46 and we'd like to introduce Teresa Ikeda.
Teresa Ikeda
Nami Inoue and me
and Arno Nakanishi
and I, Arno Nakanishi, took part in the event.
This is Blanco.
the importance of branding and its attractiveness to students.
There is a contest called “Koshien,” which is a contest to promote the importance and attractiveness of branding to students.
and we were a surprise participant in the final presentation event.
We participated in the final presentation event as a surprise.
The theme of the 13th contest was
The theme of the 13th contest was “Humanity”, and we also participated in this contest, and the theme of the 13th contest was “Humanity”.
We, as well as the other participating students
We, like the other participating students, have been thinking about the theme of “humanity” from scratch.
We, like the other participating students, have been thinking about the theme of humanity from the very beginning.
And the other day
We finally had a chance to give a presentation in front of the students.
I was able to give a presentation in front of the students.
It was a real surprise,
I was a little worried if anyone knew Nogizaka,
But I was able to give a presentation that lasted only 15 minutes or so,
Let's make a presentation that can only be done by idols, because we are idols.
Let's make it a presentation that can be done only by idols.
I had to think about it a lot.
They took it very seriously.
They were listening to me very seriously.
And they really applauded and welcomed me
They welcomed us warmly.
I was very nervous
I was nervous.
I was nervous in a good way.
I was really nervous in a good way.
I really want to affirm humanity.
The theme was learning at that time.
The theme was learning at that time, but this time the theme is a little bit different and more difficult.
We are doing it for the second time.
I think it's because we've been doing this for so long that
Theresa said in the event, “What happens once may happen three times.
I hope we can keep it alive in the future.
I'm not sure if there will be any left until then, but I'm not sure if there will be any left because it's an archive.
I'm sure you'll all remember me in the future.
I'd like to share with you some news about Nogizaka46!
Let's see!
That's a lot of news!
Okay, let's start with the first one.
Away from the hustle and bustle of the city! The members of Nogizaka46
“Nogizaka46” is a documentary TV show about the members of Nogizaka46 who travel alone together.
Season 2 of the documentary variety show “Nogizaka Escape to Nogizaka” will be available exclusively on Remina
on January 10, 2025, exclusively on Remina!
Yay for Season 2!
Lilia Ito will appear in the TRPG production Katashiro Lillive, which is being staged at the Parco Theatre.
It is an interactive table game in which the story is told through conversation,
This is a realistic and special experience.
The special features of this production are
The development and ending of the story is up to the audience's imagination
A one-time-only story is said to be created in real time at the theater
Lilia's performance will take place on Tuesday, December 24th, tomorrow.
Tuesday, December 24th, tomorrow.
The performance will be at 7:00 p.m.
Tickets are still available for purchase, so if you are interested
If you are interested, please come to the theater.
Now, let's continue,
The tickets will be on sale on January 21, 2025.
To celebrate the release of Mao Iyoki's first photo book “How to Make the Future”, we will be holding a YouTube live streaming event,
We are going to hold a live YouTube streaming on our Nogizaka Distribution channel tomorrow, Tuesday, December 24, 2012.
It's tomorrow, Tuesday, December 24th.
We will start at around 9:30pm or 7:30pm on Tuesday, December 24th.
To commemorate this event, we will be offering a B3 poster with an exclusive design only available on this channel.
Please take a look!
And one more thing.
We will be broadcasting live on Christmas Day as well!
As some of you may know, we will be broadcasting live on Christmas Day as well.
Wednesday the 25th from 10:00 p.m.
Minami Umezawa and I, Sugawara, will be doing a live broadcast on 46min TV!
As a special Christmas event, we will have a live phone call with our viewers!
Live phone call!
Yes, there will be a Christmas gift plan, and we will also have some exciting news!
We hope you enjoy the live broadcast on 24th and 25th!
Next, we would like to announce the TV program in which Nogizaka46 will appear.
On Friday, December 27th from 5:00pm to 11:10pm, Music Station Super Live 2024 will be aired on TV Asahi.
Nogizaka46 will appear on the program!
We will be performing the song “Pedestrian Bridge”.
They will be performing “Pedestrian Bridge”.
This will probably be the last show of the year for Nogizaka46.
We hope you enjoy the show!
And on Sunday, December 29th, on tbs channel 1
The 36th single “Under Live” will be aired on tbs channel 1 on Sunday, December 29th.
There will also be a documentary that goes behind the scenes of the 34th single, 35th single, and 36th single Under Live.
I hope everyone will take this opportunity to watch it!
I also participated in the 35th single as a member of the shadow side of the under song.
I would be very happy if you could watch it!
Next, on Tuesday, December 31st, the 75th NHK Kouhaku Uta Gasshogai (Red and White Song Contest) will be broadcast!
NHK Kohaku Uta Gassen on Tuesday, December 31st.
Nogizaka46 will perform “Kikkake” at the 75th NHK Kohaku Uta Gassen on Tuesday, December 31st!
Here is “Kikkake”!
In 2021
We performed Kouhaku Uta Gassen in 2021, which was the last Kouhaku Uta Gassen for Ms. Ikuta.
Actually, it was the last performance in 2021 and we, the 5th term members, had not joined the group at that time.
We had not joined Nogizaka46 yet, but we had decided to become members of Nogizaka46.
We also decided to become members of Hizaka46, and we were all watching Kohaku at home.
The song was very memorable in a different way for the students of the second term.
I hope we can perform it again in 2024, three years from now.
I'm very happy that we will be able to perform it on stage this time.
The theme of this year's Kohaku Uta Gassen is “Anata e no Uta” (Song for you), so it's a very popular song among fans.
It's an important song for us as well.
I'm very happy to be able to perform it at the Kohaku Uta Gassen with the theme of “Anata e no Uta”.
I think it's the last song in 2024.
I would like to share with you the goodness of this trigger and the greatness of the trigger that the current members convey to you.
I would like to share with you the beauty of Neko no Kikkake and the greatness of Kikkake that the current members convey.
I would like to share with you all the greatness of Neko no Kikkake and the greatness of Kikkake that the current members convey.
Please watch the Kohaku Uta Gassen.
Please watch the Kouhaku Uta Gassen and I would appreciate it if you could watch it.
Mr. Hazuki, since it's your last time, please watch the Kohaku Uta Gassen and give us your best wishes.
I look forward to seeing you at the Kohaku Uta Gassen.
Now, let's continue.
The first urban festival to be held in April 2025
Central Music & Entertainment Festival
Nogizaka46 will be performing at the Central Music & Entertainment Festival 2025!
Yes, it will be held in Yokohama for three days from Friday, April 4 to Sunday, April 6, 2025!
The festival will be held in Yokohama, including Ken Alley's Yokohama Yokohama Akarengo Run KT Zep Yokohama Hayashiguchi Park!
We will be announcing more details as they become available.
Please check out the details as well.
We hope you will pay attention to this festival!
Thank you very much!
And now, the last news!
In a message from Nogizaka46
Christmas and New Year's campaign will start soon!
Yes, first of all.
Christmas Campaign on December 25th
New Year's campaign will be held on January 1!
Yay!
Yes, from our members.
You will receive a video
and even receive a handwritten Christmas card and New Year's greeting card!
You will have a chance to receive a Christmas card and a New Year's greeting card written by our members!
Please join us!
Thank you very much for your participation!
Now, I would like to pick up a few lewks from here.
And here's the first one!
Nogizaka Higashi Aerobatics Season 2, right?
Thank you very much.
Nogizaka Higashiflight started this year.
We started this year's Nogizaka Escape to Nogizaka, and in Season 1, we showed you the journey of the members as they traveled from one place to another.
I hope you've all been watching.
Thank you very much.
Yes, actually, I was a part of Season 1.
I am here.
I'm here.
I guess it's like this.
From a junior's point of view.
I'm traveling with my seniors.
Here
It's a chance to get to know each other better.
A chance to get to know each other better.
I thought it was a great chance to get to know each other better
I thought it was a chance to get to know each other better.
and sightseeing
a little bit
We had a lot of deep conversations.
Really.
You'll be able to see a lot of people that you can only see on this show.
You'll be able to see a lot of them only on this show.
I'm sure you'll be able to see a lot of things you can only see on this show.
I hope you can look forward to Season 2.
January 10, 2025
Distribution will start at 12:00 p.m.
We will start distributing exclusively on Remina
Shizuoka and Yamanashi
It was so much fun!
I really hope that this will be a good opportunity for me
I really enjoyed talking with Kaki-san
I really started to talk with Kaki-san
I really...
I'm the youngest.
For someone so junior.
It was a great opportunity for me.
It was a chance to escape.
I got to talk to him a lot.
I hope to see more of that in Season 2.
I hope we'll be able to see more of that
I hope you will be able to see that in season 2.
We hope to see you there!
The main visual of season 1 of Aso Kore
The main visual
Teresa drew it.
I saw her drawing it.
It's amazing!
That's really good.
I said, “That's really good.
Only on East Flight.
You can't see this log.
It's really...
Theresa, we were just talking about how great you are.
I was talking with the staff.
Including the main visual.
including the main visual, and the content is really great.
Please look forward to Season 2.
To celebrate the release of Mar-chan Yuki's first photo book “How to make the future”, which will be released on January 21, 2025, we will be doing a live youtube streaming.
Tomorrow, Christmas Eve, Tuesday, December 24th at 9:30 p.m.
The live streaming will start at 9:30 p.m. tomorrow, Christmas Eve, Tuesday, December 24, on Nogizaka's live streaming channel.
In celebration of the live broadcast, we will be offering a limited edition b3 poster that is not included in the photo book as a special bonus.
In addition, to commemorate the live broadcast, you will receive a limited edition b3 poster without any folds, which is not included in the photo book.
It's really important that it's crease-free, so it'll be delivered to you.
The photo book will be changed tomorrow, December 24th, from midnight, not 1:00 p.m. on the 24th, which is very short.
It's a very short window of time, 24 hours from midnight to 11:59 p.m. on the 24th, so you have a little bit of time.
So please check out the official account.
So please check out the official account and check it out.
So be sure to check out our official account and check it out.
So please check it out.
24:00.
from midnight.
Lots of people.
Ladies and Gentlemen...
What did we call you? Stand by...
Keep the feed open for a second.
Stand by.
Soon after midnight, you'll be able to make a purchase.
But you have until 11:59 p.m. to do so.
Oh, it's out of focus.
I'm really looking forward to seeing your photo book.
She's so cute. She's cute.
We're in the same year, so we're in the same year... well, we did a photo book together for the 5th term,
I feel like a mother when it's just one of each of us.
I feel like a mother. I feel like I'm going to be looking at them and saying how cute they are.
I don't know much about the content yet, so I'll be looking forward to it until the day it goes on sale.
I'm so excited! So the live broadcast of the release of Mar-chan Yuki's photo book will be held on Christmas Eve.
But the next day, Christmas Day, we'll be doing a live broadcast as well.
The next day, Christmas Day, we'll be doing another live broadcast.
December 25th
Wednesday, December 25th at 10:00 p.m.
Miki's Minami Umezawa and
Minami Umezawa of Miki and myself, Sugawara.
46 minutes TV” with Ms. Minami Umezawa of Miki and myself, Sugawara.
It's a live broadcast!
Yay!
This time, we're going to do a 46 minutes TV show.
This time, we'll be doing a special Christmas event.
I'll be dressed as Nogizaka Santa Claus.
Ume-san and I will have a live phone call with our viewers
and we'll send you some presents.
We'll also have some exciting news for you!
We will be talking about the B news that is a regular topic of the live call
We are planning to have a live call on the theme of “B news”.
In other words, we are working on it!
We are still looking for participants for the live call project, so if you have any B news you would like to tell us, please let us know.
If you have any B news you would like to share with us
If you have any B news that you would like to share with us on the live phone, please feel free to do so.
Please visit the youtube streaming page or the official website of
If you have any B news you would like to share with us, please apply through the Youtube streaming page or the official website of Nogizaka46.
It's going to be a very exciting live broadcast, so let's spend a wonderful Christmas together!
I'm looking forward to it.
Renren
I'm actually wearing a catsuit in this thumbnail.
I chose to wear a reindeer.
So...
Ume-san's was a fusion of a reindeer and a Santa.
It was like a fusion of reindeer and Santa Claus.
It suited her very well.
Please come and join us on the 25th
Please join us from 10:00 p.m. on the 25th.
Thank you very much!
Next, let's go to the next page.
This is the campaign information of Nogizaka46 Messages!
The other day, we held a free high reading campaign.
Thank you very much for your support.
We hope you enjoyed the members' talk.
Thank you very much.
Did you enjoy my talk? Thank you very much.
I wonder if any of you took the opportunity to take a picture of me.
I didn't have any comments.
No comments.
Please leave a comment on YouTube.
There's also a hashtag.
I hope you got it.
Yeah, me too.
I've been taking
I take a lot of selfies, and I take a lot of pictures of me and the members just messing around.
The announcement of the vice captain was made during Thanksgiving, so those who took my messages for the first time during the free lecture campaign may have been surprised to see my daily messages.
I mean, you know, there was a bunch of messages, and then a barrage of messages...
I just sent a message.
I sent a little bit of a message, so...
I guess I surprised a lot of people.
I'm sure I surprised a lot of people.
I'm having a lot of fun.
I wonder if there are people who got all of them.
I wonder if there are.
By the way, in addition to the free code campaign, a while ago, I took advantage of the Nogizaka46 message campaign.
I've been a fan of Nogizaka46 for a long time. I've taken a picture of all of them.
I'm still taking pictures of some of the members, but there was a time when I took pictures of about 30 members of Nogizaka46.
There was a time when I took pictures of all of them.
It's fun, isn't it?
It's fun to send them, too.
But it's also fun to send them to each of them because you can see who they are.
I could see what they were doing today.
I got to know them a little bit.
I was enjoying it as a fan.
So that's the kind of message app I'm talking about.
What kind of message app is this?
It's the kind of messaging app that makes fans happy.
We're happy to announce that we'll be starting a Christmas and New Year campaign soon!
Christmas and New Year's campaigns will start soon!
First of all, we will start the Christmas campaign on December 25th and the New Year campaign on January 1st. The Christmas campaign will start on December 25th, and the New Year's campaign will start on January 1st.
In the Christmas Campaign, you will receive a video from a subscribed member on the morning of December 25.
You will also have a chance to win a Christmas card personally handwritten by a member who is subscribed at that time.
In the New Year's campaign, you will receive a video from a high reading member on the morning of January 1.
You will receive a video from a high reading member.
You will also have a chance to win a personalized New Year's greeting card written by a member of Takayomi.
Please take this opportunity to enjoy Nogizaka46 Messages!
Let's enjoy it more and more!
Yes, I've already written both of your messages.
Whose hand will it be?
Who's going to get it?
Please let me know if you received them.
Yes, the Christmas card.
A personalized Christmas card.
If you're one of the winners of the Christmas card...
You might receive it before the end of the year.
You might get it before the end of the year.
It's a Christmas present.
In a way.
I hope you're looking forward to it.
And the video.
You'll be able to see them.
The members who are subscribers.
You can watch the video and you'll receive
Christmas present and
I don't know what New Year's is.
I think it's a New Year's gift
New Year's gift is not a New Year's present.
You can also watch the video and have a chance to win a Christmas card and a New Year's greeting card.
Peco
You can see this video of my own... I get one on my birthday.
Happy Birthday!
It's a strange experience to be wished a happy birthday by myself.
Maybe this is my Christmas movie.
Maybe I'll come and say Merry Christmas to myself.
I'm so excited!
I wish you all the best for the 25th and the 1st!
Well, it's almost time for me to end.
I know today was a bit of a recording session.
I hope you all had a good time.
It was a lot of fun.
You're still cute on the set.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
And now, finally, with this week's pickup news.
I'd like to do some screentime.
Here it is.
very important!
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'll make a video.
Here's the video!
Here's a pose.
Five.
Four.
Three.
I don't know if you have any Santa poses, but we have New Year's coming up, so 4 3 2 1
I don't know if there's a Santa pose or not? But there's New Year's too.
Kagamimochi
I'm so sorry.
Okay, what should we do now?
This is the live broadcast of the 25th.
Oh no, it's Santa too!
Oh no, what should I do?
Oh, no...
I'm not going to do it.
Let's go!
Three.
Three...
One.
Yes, I'd be happy to.
I look forward to working with you.
Please take a look
Looking forward to it
Please look forward to it
Yes, so this video will be archived until next Monday!
If you feel like taking a look back...
I'd be happy if you could take a look back.
I mean...
If you want to see Sacchan's face...
I'd be happy if you could open this video if you'd like to look back at it or if you'd like to see Sacchan's face.
I would be very happy if you could open this video if you want to look back or if you want to see her face.
And next time
The next issue of Weekly Gisaka News will be on Monday, December 30th.
Monday, December 30th
The last one before the end of the year.
We are planning to distribute it on Monday, December 30th.
We are planning to do a live distribution
We are planning to do a live broadcast
But due to scheduling conflicts
There is a possibility that it will be recorded.
We will let you know when the time is fixed.
We will let you know when it is decided.
We will let you know as soon as the time is fixed.
Please check back soon!
Of course, next week will be the last one of the year.
Sugawara will be the MC.
He'll be wearing glasses and a uniform.
I'll be wearing glasses and a uniform.
That's right, tomorrow.
The day after tomorrow is Christmas Eve.
Christmas Day...
NogizakaDistribution will continue with live broadcasts.
So please check it out.
That's three days in a row!
Wow!
That means it's Christmas Eve and Christmas Eve.
Please enjoy the show!
I'm sorry I've been on a bit of a bender.
I had a great time.
I missed your comments.
I hope to see you all next week when we will be broadcasting live again, and I would appreciate your comments.
See you next week!
Bye bye!
Thank you.